Ofir Tako

Tel Aviv | 054-3332240 | ofirtako@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/ofir-tako

Please visit my web for additional info : www.ofirtako.com

Summary

A result oriented professional with 7 years of experience in virtualization, Building images, programming and customer service. As a delivery engineer, I have managed and deployed complex projects for a wide range of customers focusing on high availability and performance.

In the recent year I've been certified by DevOps Experts college as Junior DevOps Engineer, the course gave me knowledge in using relevant tools to perform full CI / CD processes, configuration management and container orchestration. I am a quick learner, team player and a skilled communicator who embraces challenges and creative problem solving with an entrepreneurial attitude.

Work Experience

Service Delivery Engineer - Maccabi Health Care / DevOps Junior - Tictuk 2017 - Present

- Implements testing environment using Selenium Python & Kubernetes Tictuk
- Maintenance of the app based on AWS cloud infrastructure Tictuk
- Virtualization Management automation for creating & configuring vms using Powershell scripts Maccabi
- Building & Deploying Images for enterprise workstations Maccabi

SysAdmin - Leumi Card

2015 - 2017

- Deploying applications and security updates on production systems.
- End User Computing management Virtual Desktops, GPO, DNS & DHCP.
- Implementing Monitoring and Automation system in the enterprize Systrack Platform.

IT - Ness Technologies

2013 - 2015

- Maintenance of endpoints workstations using scripts.
- Working with Cisco switches and routers TCP / IP.
- Install and Configure Printers servers for the enterprise.

Project Manager - Ranad -Tech

2011 - 2013

- Installing company's product for customers Clock based Attendance system.
- Building SQL Queries & reports.
- Providing ongoing assistance and solutions for customers needs.

Telephone Sales Representative - Partner communications

2009 - 2011

IDF Service - Computer Training Team Leader

2006 - 2009

Education.

2019 - DevOps (DevOps Experts College)

• 2016 - SCCM 2012 R2 Microsoft Certified (CBT Nuggets)

2017 / 2018 - Python , Powershell 4.0 (John Bryce) • 2015 - MCSA + CCNA (Ness College)

Technical Skills

Languages: Python, Powershell, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Bash, SQL.

DB: Microsoft SQL, MySQL, MongoDB

OS: Microsoft Windows / Server, MacOS, Linux.

Virtualization & Cloud: AWS, Docker, Kubernetes, VMWare Vcenter, Hyper-V.

Miscellaneous: Jenkins, Git, Github, Bitbucket, Ansible, Selenium, Nginx, Flask, Terraform.

Additional skills

Self-study

Good Human Relations

Initiative and open minded

Visionary

Ability to inspire individuals to realize goals

Other Details

Year of Birth: 1988 Homeland: ISRAEL Marital status: SINGLE

Languages:

Hebrew - Native language

English - Advanced

Spanish - Basic

Other Interests:

Music, Graphic Design.